SIMIN ANARAKI

Please visit portfolio at: www.simin.uk

• Great Yarmouth, UK
• (+44) 07818161573

 \times

Simin.Anaraki@gmail.com

1

www.linkedin.com/in/Simin-Angraki

ABOUT ME



I am a computer engineer with over 6 years' experience in the IT industry and finally managed to undertake training to become a developer which I am very passionate about. I have consistently demonstrated a commitment to excellence, a passion for technology, and a relentless drive for self-improvement, which led me to embarking on an exciting transition into the realm of web development, aligning with my profound interest in the digital landscape. This transformation coincided with my relocation to the United Kingdom in February 2022, adding a global dimension to my expertise. I've acquired skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Sass, and Bootstrap which is essential when working as a front-end developer. I am now looking to use my skills and experiences to gain a rewarding job role, where I learn and develop to help me within my career.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



Full time student

Coding Bootcamp

03/2023 - Present

- Studied Front-End Developer
- Programmed and developed websites to build a portfolio.
- Self-study essential skills for front end development.
- Actively attended multiple seminars and conference to build up knowledge and experience.

IT Coordinator

KDT

05/2019 - 08/2021

www.kdt.ir

- Used active listening and relationship-building skills to assess customer needs, build rapport and deliver viable solutions.
- Highlighted product features in line with customer needs, securing high-value sales.
- Used active listening and relationship-building techniques to assess customer needs and deliver viable solutions.
- Maximized sales revenue through effective upselling of associated products.

Hardware IT Technician

ASUS warranty service

05/2015 - 03/2019

- Executed well-informed critical decision making in high-pressure situations.
- Observed manuals and instructions to effectively install and troubleshoot devices.
- Planned, scheduled, and delegated daily tasks, consistently meeting demands on technical support teams.
- Conducted tests and inspections to QA/QC standards.

EDUCATION



- ✓ Bachelor of Computer technology Tehran, Iran 2012
- ✓ Front-End Developer Coding Bootcamp Coding Front 2023

Technical Skills

- ✓ HTML
- ✓ CSS
- ✓ JavaScript
- ✓ React
- ✓ Sass
- ✓ Bootstrap
- ✓ Git

I'm holding professional diplomas for these bullet points as well.

Other Skills

- Quality Control
- Assembly process
- ✓ Manufacturing
- ✓ Organizational skills
- ✓ Issue analysis
- ✓ Reporting
- ✓ Team Player
- ✓ Problem Solving
- Detail oriented
- ✓ Communication skills
- ✓ Strong work ethic
- ✓ Hard worker

Hobbies and Interests

- ✓ Watching Movies
- ✓ Listening to music
- ✓ Programming
- ✓ Exercise and
- ✓ Crafting with wood